Damn
젠장
"(Tae Ho Choi)"
"(최태호)"
"Mr. Oh, Yang Jung Hwang, Do Young Lee, Hyun Joo."
"오씨, 황양정씨, 이도영씨, 현주씨."
Won't you come home?
집에 오지 않을래?
I was looking for a house, sir.
저는 집을 찾고 있었습니다.
Oh God. It's not easy to find a home these days.
오 맙소사. 요즘 집 구하기가 쉽지 않네요.
What about a honeymoon?
신혼여행은 어때요?
My wife wants to go to Paris but I don't think we can go because of Covid.
아내가 파리에 가고 싶어하는데 코로나 때문에 갈 수 없을 것 같아요.
Woe to him. What a fucking virus.
그에게 화가 있다. 정말 빌어먹을 바이러스야.
Why did you come this late?
왜 이렇게 늦게 왔나요?
Listen
듣다
There is a big issue.
큰 문제가 있습니다.
I have been monitoring a loan shark for nearly six months,
저는 거의 6개월 동안 사채업자를 모니터링해 왔는데,
This scoundrel films clips of people and threatens them with them.
이 악당은 사람들의 영상을 촬영하고 위협합니다.
I came across a list of the scoundrel's victims today.
오늘 그 악당의 희생자 명단을 접했습니다.
I will share the data with you, so we can check it in detail together.
자료를 공유해드릴테니 함께 자세히 확인해보세요.
Okay sir.
알겠습니다.
- Get back to what you're doing. - Okay.
- 하던 일로 돌아가세요 - 알았어
Okay
좋아요
He said he received the list today.
오늘 명단을 받았다고 하더군요.
He probably didn't do this alone.
아마 그 사람 혼자 이 일을 한 게 아니었을 거예요.
Find someone who participated in this and I will pay you 100 million per person.
이에 참여한 분을 찾아주시면 1인당 1억씩 지급해 드리겠습니다 .
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
When will you know where In Mok Oh is?
오인목이 어디 있는지 언제 알 수 있나요?
I'll be able to see where he used his credit card,
그 사람이 신용카드를 어디에 썼는지 알 수 있을 거예요 .
In the last seven days by tomorrow morning.
지난 7일 동안 내일 아침까지요.
I will send you the money as soon as I receive the address. Good luck
주소 받는대로 돈 보내드리겠습니다 . 행운을 빌어요
100 million.
1억.
how's it going
어떻게되고 있습니까
Jang Do was the only one who knew where the hard drive was.
하드디스크가 어디에 있는지 아는 사람 은 장도뿐이었다 .
The bastard revealed his whereabouts when Boss Choi caught him.
그 놈은 최보스가 붙잡자 자신의 행방을 공개했다.
The scoundrels who were with him at that time allied themselves with Director Hong.
당시 그와 함께 있던 악당들은 홍 감독과 동맹을 맺었다.
"Myung-gil."
"명길."
Secure one hard drive?
하나의 하드 드라이브를 확보하시겠습니까?
There is only one solid-state drive.
솔리드 스테이트 드라이브가 하나만 있습니다.
But there is a backup copy of everything on the laptop
하지만 노트북에는 모든 내용의 백업 복사본이 있습니다.
Which we used to transfer videos to the hard drive.
우리는 비디오를 하드 드라이브로 전송하는 데 사용했습니다.
Good
좋은
We must not act at the moment.
우리는 지금 당장 행동해서는 안 됩니다.
If we posted the video at the wrong time,
영상을 잘못된 시간에 게시했다면,
That bastard Hong,
그 새끼 홍,
It will harm our company with tax audit.
세무조사로 인해 우리 회사에 피해가 갈 것입니다.
Myung Gil,
명길,
Wouldn't it be better to let them know you still have the video?
아직 영상이 남아있다고 알려주는 것이 더 낫지 않을까요 ?
Work to scare them so they stop fooling around.
겁을 주어 장난을 그만 두도록 하세요.
How smart you are.
당신은 얼마나 똑똑합니다.
Let's have a toast.
건배하자.
- To you.
- 당신에게
"Address, market, gas station, rice shop"
"주소, 시장, 주유소, 밥가게"
"Gohong Grocery"
"고홍식료품점"
Did you see him?
그 사람 봤었 어?
I'm not sure. Customers wear masks, so I'm not sure.
잘 모르겠습니다. 손님들이 마스크를 착용하고 있어서 잘 모르겠네요.
Understood. Is that so then?
이해했다. 그렇다면 그렇습니까?
Damn, unbelievable.
젠장, 믿을 수 없군요.
Take another look.
다시 한번 살펴보세요.
I don't know
모르겠습니다
Do you find this funny?
이게 재미있다고 생각하시나요?
- Excuse me? - You find this funny?
- 실례합니다? - 이게 재미있나요?
No, I don't find it so.
아니요, 저는 그렇게 생각하지 않습니다.
the curse
저주
Look away, you bastard.
멀리 봐, 이 개자식아.
Take a closer look. do you know him
자세히 살펴보세요. 그를 아니
I don't know
모르겠습니다
Do you know him or not, you scoundrel? Get up, do you know him or not?
그 사람을 아는가, 모르느냐, 이 악당아? 일어나세요, 당신은 그를 아시나요, 모르시나요?
- I don't know. - No?
- 모르겠어요 - 아니?
Look carefully, you bastard. Do you know him or not?
잘 봐, 이 새끼야. 당신은 그를 아시나요, 모르시나요?
the bastard
그 놈
- Shit. - I should kill you, you bastard.
- 젠장 - 죽여야겠어, 이 새끼야.
Look closely.
잘 봐봐.
Hello sir
안녕하세요 선생님
Hello, welcome
안녕하세요 반갑습니다
- May I ask you something? - Sure.
- 뭐 하나 물어봐도 될까요? - 물론이죠.
I'm looking for someone, he's my father's friend.
누군가를 찾고 있는데 그 사람은 내 아버지 친구예요.
Yes, I know this person.
네, 저는 이 사람을 압니다.
- Really? - I know him, why do you want him?
- 정말요? - 그 사람을 알아요, 왜 그 사람을 원하는 거죠?
I'm getting married and I wanted to invite him to the wedding.
제가 결혼을 하는데 그 사람을 결혼식에 초대하고 싶었어요.
Good
좋은
Do you know his address?
그 사람 주소를 아시나요?
naturally. I deliver rice there every month.
당연히. 매달 그곳으로 쌀을 배달해요.
May I take his address?
그 사람 주소를 물어봐도 될까요?
certainly. I'll tell you about it.
틀림없이. 나는 그것에 대해 당신에게 말할 것입니다.
"Catch outside the ring"
"링 밖에서 잡아라"
"(Stone Village)"
"(돌마을)"
Here he is.
여기 있습니다.
In Beom Kang's file.
강범의 파일에.
I have everything I need to know about him here.
여기에 대해 내가 알아야 할 모든 것이 있습니다.
You get your work done quickly.
당신은 일을 빨리 끝내게 됩니다.
Speed ​​is important in such matters.
이러한 문제에서는 속도가 중요합니다.
- Thanks. - Excuse me.
- 고마워요 - 실례해요
- It's done. - Yes.
- 끝났어요 - 네
Is that all?
그게 다야?
Sorry
죄송합니다
You don't know then.
그러면 당신은 모릅니다.
Normally, when someone is assigned to carry out a request like this,
일반적으로 누군가가 이와 같은 요청을 수행하도록 지정되면
Offered as a token of thanks.
감사의 표시로 제공됩니다.
Good. How much should we pay you?
좋은. 우리는 당신에게 얼마를 지불해야 합니까?
Well, a lot.
글쎄요.
We're a team and a family now and a generous tip would do me good.
이제 우리는 한 팀이자 가족이므로 넉넉한 팁을 주면 도움이 될 것입니다.
- Well, here you go. - Yes.
- 음, 여기요 - 네
Thanks
감사해요
Call me anytime.
언제든지 전화주세요.
- We will. Good day. - Goodbye.
- 그럴게요. 좋은 하루 되세요 - 안녕.
Good
좋은
"Ten thousand won"
"만원"
Damn, I meant a million won.
젠장, 내 말은 백만 원이라니.
"Personal information, In Beom Kang."
"개인정보 강인범입니다."
She asked us not to use it.
그녀는 우리에게 그것을 사용하지 말라고 요청했습니다.
But it's worth taking a look at his neighborhood on a big screen.
하지만 그의 동네를 큰 화면으로 살펴보는 것은 가치가 있다 .
What do we do if Da Min comes?
다민이 오면 어떡하지?
You won't come. She happened to stop by the last time she checked us out.
당신은 오지 않을 것입니다. 그녀는 마지막으로 우리를 확인했을 때 우연히 들렀습니다 .
It was bad luck.
불운이었습니다.
Look
바라보다
- “Gangdong-gu,” “Seongro-ro.” - “Seonggo-ro.”
- “강동구”, “성로로” - “성고로”
I told you she would come. Turn it off.
나는 그녀가 올 것이라고 말했다. 그것을 끄십시오.
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
The place had the smell of miserable men.
그 곳에서는 비참한 남자들의 냄새가 났다.
Why did you repeat your action?
왜 당신의 행동을 반복했습니까?
Go to an internet café.
인터넷 카페에 가보세요.
We are sorry.
미안 해요.
We also apologize for the smell of misery.
또한 비참한 냄새에 대해 사과드립니다.
the curse
저주
It doesn't matter. The room was already messed up.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다. 방은 이미 엉망이 되어 있었다.
I was spoiled.
나는 버릇없었다.
"Da who"!
"다 누구"!
- What? - I apologize for what happened today.
- 뭐? - 오늘 일어난 일에 대해 사과드립니다.
I'll take care of that smell.
그 냄새는 제가 처리할게요.
how
어떻게
Air distributor.
공기 분배기.
An air diffuser will get rid of that miserable old man smell.
디퓨저는 그 비참한 노인 냄새를 제거해 줄 것입니다.
truly
진심으로
First, to get rid of the smell, you must find an anti-odor.
먼저 냄새를 없애기 위해서는 냄새방지제를 찾아야 합니다.
The scent of Misery is a mixture of intense musky scent
미저리의 향은 강렬한 머스크향이 섞인 향이에요
And an unintended smell of rotting firewood.
그리고 의도치 않게 썩어가는 장작 냄새.
To get rid of them, we need a counter odor.
그것들을 제거하려면 역취가 필요합니다.
Floral and fruity scent.
꽃향기와 과일향.
I use Bice wax and Diptyque fragrance.
저는 바이스 왁스와 딥티크 향을 사용합니다.
- I like this idea. - That's good.
- 이 아이디어 마음에 들어요 - 좋아요
It's a great
정말 대단해요
The refreshing sweetness of Pace wax will wash away
페이스왁스의 상큼한 달콤함이 씻어내줍니다
The smell of antique misery is about the place here.
이곳에는 고풍스러운 비참함의 냄새가 풍깁니다.
We'll get one for you when we leave here.
우리가 여기서 떠날 때 하나 사줄게.
- A gift. - Yes.
- 선물이에요 - 네
We'll get two, for the upstairs and downstairs.
위층과 아래층에 두 개를 구하겠습니다.
And for the bathroom too.
그리고 욕실에도 마찬가지입니다.
Well, whatever you want.
글쎄, 당신이 원하는대로.
We agreed
우리는 동의했다
How does In Beom Kang know my number? Look at this.
강인범이 내 번호를 어떻게 알아? 이것 좀 봐.
unbelievable
믿을 수 없는
Something is definitely wrong.
확실히 뭔가 잘못되었습니다.
What's wrong with my grandfather?
할아버지에게 무슨 문제가 있나요?
Who did this to him?
누가 그에게 이런 짓을 했나요?
In reality
실제로는
Listen...
듣다...
Come to Four Garden Shopping Center in Incheon in an hour.
한 시간이면 인천 포가든 쇼핑센터로 오세요 .
If you call the police, the elderly person will die.
경찰에 신고하면 노인이 사망합니다.
I will kill you, you motherfucker.
널 죽여버릴 거야, 이 새끼야.
Listen...
듣다...
You need to tell us what else he said, Da Min.
그 사람이 또 무슨 말을 했는지 말해줘야 해요, 다민.
He asked me to go to Four Garden in an hour.
그는 나에게 한 시간 후에 Four Garden에 가라고 요청했습니다.
If we call the police...
경찰에 신고하면...
My grandfather would be killed, he said.
그는 내 할아버지를 죽일 것이라고 말했다.
Let's hurry. There is no time.
서두르 자. 시간이 없습니다.
- “Gunwoo.” - Yes?
- “건우.” - 네?
- How many men do you think there will be? - At least 30?
- 남자는 몇 명 정도 될까요? - 적어도 30명 정도는 될까요?
They will most likely be armed.
그들은 아마도 무장하고 있을 것입니다.
In Beom Kang and this guy, Jung, will be there.
강인범이랑 정이라는 사람이 있을 거에요.
Should we call Gang Young?
강영에게 전화할까?
No, this would put Mr. Oh in great danger.
아니요, 그렇게 되면 오씨가 큰 위험에 빠지게 됩니다.
What about our eldest?
우리 큰형은요?
Which big?
어느 것이 큰가요?
Mr. Moon.
문 씨.
But he was injured in his arm.
그러나 그는 팔에 부상을 입었습니다.
Wouldn't he help in any way possible?
그 사람이 어떤 식으로든 도와주지 않을까요?
This is true but...
이것은 사실입니다만...
Are you ready?
준비 되었나요?
Yes, but what's the need for a bow, Da Min?
응, 그런데 활이 무슨 필요가 있어, 다민?
To save my grandfather.
할아버지를 구하기 위해.
This is completely unacceptable. The situation is very dangerous, just the two of us will go.
이것은 완전히 용납될 수 없습니다. 상황은 매우 위험합니다. 우리 둘만 갈 것입니다.
Step aside.
비켜서 다.
No, Da Min...
아니, 다민아...
- What... - Wait.
- 뭐... - 잠깐만요.
I can help with my style.
내 스타일에 도움을 줄 수 있어요.
I will go and do not negotiate. Do not deter me.
나는 가서 협상하지 않을 것입니다. 나를 단념하지 마십시오.
Let's go. We don't have time.
갑시다. 시간이 없어요.
She is a skilled marksman.
그녀는 숙련된 사수입니다.
Listen
듣다
I think it will benefit us.
나는 그것이 우리에게 도움이 될 것이라고 생각합니다.
This is Woo Jin, sir.
우진씨입니다.
mr oh
오 씨
He has been kidnapped.
그는 납치되었습니다.
Can you help us in any way?
어떤 식으로든 우리를 도와주실 수 있나요?
I am also indebted to Mr. Oh.
나 역시 오씨에게 빚을 지고 있다.
Don't go without me no matter what.
무슨 일이 있어도 나 없이 가지 마세요.
it's a command
그것은 명령이다
"Gwang Mu-mun, 734th Senior Division."
"광무문, 734고위사단."
Are the two younger Marines ready?
두 젊은 해병대는 준비됐나요?
- Yes, sir. - You did your best to prepare, sir.
- 예, 선생님 - 최선을 다해 준비하셨습니다.
I put it on because it was left at home. It's itchy.
집에 두고 온거라 꼈는데 가려워요.
I think it's old.
오래된 것 같아요.
Get out before the warts start to appear.
사마귀가 나타나기 전에 나가십시오.
I will enter from the parking lot...
주차장에서 들어갈게요...
Who are you
누구세요
I came to save my grandfather.
할아버지를 구하러 왔습니다.
She is Mr. Oh's granddaughter.
그녀는 오씨의 손녀이다.
Understood. Good
이해했다. 좋은
You have his facial features.
당신은 그의 얼굴 특징을 가지고 있습니다.
An hour passed.
한 시간이 지났습니다.
Okay but what is that bag?
알았어, 그런데 그 가방은 뭐야?
It is a compound bow.
컴파운드보우 입니다.
compound
화합물
Rather, it is a compound bow.
오히려 컴파운드 활이다.
Arc...
호...
It's an archer's bow, sir.
궁수의 활입니다, 선생님.
correct. Koreans are good at archery.
옳은. 한국 사람들은 양궁을 잘해요.
Is she skilled?
그녀는 능숙합니까?
Yes
예
Okay, me and the archer are going up the stairs from the parking lot
좋아, 나와 궁수는 주차장에서 계단을 올라가고 있다
We head to the top of the building.
우리는 건물 꼭대기로 향합니다.
And you two Marines will enter through the front door.
그리고 두 해병이 정문을 통해 들어갈 것입니다.
We'll protect you from above, okay?
우리가 위에서 널 지켜줄게, 알았지?
- Your order, sir. - Let's move.
- 명령입니다 - 이동합시다
- Follow me. - Okay.
- 따라오세요 - 알았어
- From here.
- 여기서부터
Where is Mr. Oh?
오씨는 어디 계시나요?
Kill them!
그들을 죽여 버려!
Damn
젠장
one two Three
하나 둘 셋
the curse
저주
- What? - Where was he thrown from?
- 뭐라구요? - 그 사람은 어디서 쫓겨났어요?
Where was he thrown from?
그는 어디서 쫓겨났나요?
What a wonderful archer you are.
당신은 정말 훌륭한 궁수입니다.
- Catch them! - Who is this?
- 잡아라 - 누구죠?
above
~ 위에
- Great. - Where?
- 좋아요 - 어디요?
What? What is this
무엇? 이게 뭔가요
Hey, stop!
그만해!
above
~ 위에
Who wears black clothes there?
거기 누가 검은 옷을 입나요?
Who throws? Who does this?
누가 던지나요? 누가 이런 일을 하나요?
Who's wearing blue over there?
저기 파란색 옷 입은 사람 누구야?
Damn
젠장
Keep helping the Marines, okay?
해병대를 계속 도와주세요. 알았죠?
Oh blue color.
아 블루 컬러.
Were you on one of the running teams?
당신은 달리기 팀 중 하나에 속해 있었나요?
Screw it.
나사로 고정.
Get away from here!
여기에서 떠나세요!
he is coming! Make way for him!
그가 온다! 그를 위해 길을 비켜주세요!
They got him!
그 사람들이 그를 잡았어요!
Damn
젠장
What do you do? stand up
너 뭐하니? 일어서다
the curse
저주
Damn
젠장
You are worthless without your knife.
칼이 없으면 당신은 쓸모가 없습니다.
Take it out of its sheath, you bastard.
칼집에서 꺼내라, 이 개자식아.
let it out
그것을 보자
I see you have pride.
보니 자부심이 있으신 것 같아요.
Come closer then.
그럼 가까이 오세요.
Are you okay sir?
괜찮으세요 선생님?
I'm not fine at all.
나는 전혀 괜찮지 않다.
one two three four
하나 둘 셋 넷
Oh running!
아 달려요!
You scoundrel. We don't have time. Wake up.
이 악당. 시간이 없어요. 깨우다.
Where is Mr. Oh?
오씨는 어디 계시나요?
Look at this bastard, he gives the old marine a terrifying look.
이 놈 좀 봐, 늙은 해병에게 무서운 표정을 짓는구나.
- Archer, give me an arrow. - What?
- 궁수님, 화살 좀 주세요 - 뭐라고요?
Don't worry. Give me an arrow for a moment.
괜찮아요. 잠시만 화살을 주세요.
This bastard is a loyal troll.
이 놈은 충성스러운 트롤이에요.
I was like you too,
나도 당신과 같았어요
When Mr. Choi was among us.
최씨가 우리 중에 있었을 때.
Do you know what happens to a troll who loses his master?
주인을 잃은 트롤에게 무슨 일이 일어나는지 아시나요?
He loses his way and attacks anyone he sees!
그는 길을 잃고 눈에 띄는 사람을 공격합니다!
Don't worry, you're fine.
걱정하지 마세요. 괜찮습니다.
You are experiencing psychological trauma and are not in pain.
당신은 심리적 트라우마를 겪고 있으며 고통을 느끼지 않습니다.
Actual pain
실제 통증
You will feel it when you take it off!
벗으면 느낌이 옵니다!
Marine,
선박,
Cover the archer's ears, please.
궁수의 귀를 막아주세요.
You're not married, right?
당신은 결혼하지 않았죠?
Good
좋은
Family is the most important thing a person has in his life.
가족은 사람이 인생에서 갖는 가장 중요한 것입니다.
But without this, you will be unable to start a family.
하지만 이것이 없으면 가족을 꾸릴 수 없습니다.
Work or family. Choose
직장이나 가족. 선택하다
If you insist on choosing work, even in this situation,
이런 상황에서도 굳이 직업 선택을 고집한다면 ,
I will admit that you are truly professional.
당신이 진정한 전문가임을 인정하겠습니다.
But in return, I will pierce your balls for you.
하지만 그 대가로 나는 당신을 위해 당신의 불알을 뚫을 것입니다.
Why
왜
Because I'm a professional person too.
나도 전문적인 사람이니까.
What will be your choice?
당신의 선택은 무엇입니까?
I'll give you three seconds.
3초의 시간을 드리겠습니다.
three
삼
two
둘
One
하나
- Hey! - What? Why
- 이봐요 - 뭐? 왜
I will speak, sir.
제가 얘기하겠습니다.
Lower your head.
머리를 낮추십시오.
Get on, fast!
빨리 타세요!
I said keep your head down.
나는 고개를 숙이라고 말했다.
We're going to rescue Mr. Oh. Can you spare In Beom Kang?
우리가 오씨를 구출할 예정인데 강인범을 살려주실 수 있나요?
What are you saying? I have to go too.
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야? 나도 가야 해요.
We will do this ourselves.
우리는 이것을 스스로 할 것입니다.
Your arm is in critical condition, sir.
팔이 심각한 상태입니다.
Damn, this is unbelievable.
젠장, 이건 말도 안 되는 일이야.
Sir, In Beom Kang knows where Myung Gil Kim is secretly hiding money,
강인범 선생님은 김명길이 돈을 숨겨둔 곳을 알고 계시고,
He knows the location of the safe and the money in it , and he knows where Mr. Choi's gold was hidden.
그는 금고와 그 안에 들어 있는 돈의 위치를 ​​알고 있으며, 최씨의 금이 어디에 숨겨져 있는지도 알고 있다.
Please extract all this information from him using the spirit of the Navy.
해군의 정신을 사용하여 그에게서 이 모든 정보를 추출해 주십시오 .
Please sir.
부탁드립니다 선생님.
OK I will do it
그래, 할게
Save Mr. Oh no matter what.
무슨 일이 있어도 오씨를 구해주세요.
Your order, sir.
주문하셨습니다.
Let's go. Get on, Da Min.
갑시다. 어서, 다민.
"National Police Agency"
"경찰청"
here
여기
How does this look to you?
이것이 당신에게 어떻게 보이나요?
Sir, I've seen him standing next to the Blue House chief of staff before.
선생님, 청와대 비서실장 옆에 서 있는 것을 본 적이 있습니다 .
- Chief of Staff? - Yes, sir.
- 참모총장? - 네, 그렇습니다.
That hooked nose and ears. I am sure
그 매부리코와 귀. 나는 확신한다
Why would a moneylender pay a bribe to the presidential office?
대금업자가 왜 청와대에 뇌물을 주겠는가.
Maybe he likes to snoop?
어쩌면 그는 스누핑을 좋아할까요?
Or does it have a bigger role than we realize?
아니면 우리가 생각하는 것보다 더 큰 역할을 하는 걸까요?
"Drunk Gun Woo"
"술 취한 건우"
Welcome
환영
Welcome. I apologize for calling so late
환영. 너무 늦게 전화해서 미안해요
But we didn't know what to do, so I called.
그런데 어떻게 해야 할지 몰라서 전화를 했어요.
- What's going on? - Myung-gil kidnapped Mr. Oh.
- 무슨 일이에요? - 명길이 오씨를 납치했어요.
I'm heading to Seoryong with Woo-jin now.
나는 지금 우진이와 함께 서룡으로 향하고 있다.
Just the two of you?
둘만요?
Why did you tell me this now?
왜 지금 나한테 그런 말을 한 거야?
I apologize for this but they said they would kill Mr. Oh if we reported it to the police.
죄송하지만 경찰에 신고하면 오씨를 죽인다고 하더군요.
Wait.
기다리다.
Did Myung Gil Kim contact you personally?
김명길 씨가 직접 연락을 했나?
No, we caught one of his henchmen and he told us so.
아니요, 우리는 그의 부하 중 한 명을 잡았고 그는 우리에게 그렇게 말했습니다.
So you don't know for sure if Kim was there?
그럼 김씨가 거기에 있었는지 확실히 모르시나요 ?
This is correct
이것이 맞습니다
send me the site. I'm heading over there. Don't barge in and wait for me.
나에게 사이트를 보내주세요. 나 저쪽으로 갈게, 끼어들지 말고 기다려.
Good
좋은
- Send him the website, Woo Jin. - Okay.
- 그에게 웹사이트를 보내줘, 우진 - 알았어.
- Yes, sir. - “Jae Min.”
- 네, 선생님 - "재민이요."
Come to the conference room immediately.
당장 회의실로 오세요.
Your order, sir.
주문하셨습니다.
"Meeting Room No. 1"
"1번 회의실"
Ask for support, Jae Min. The place is in Buseongmyeon, Seoryong.
재민아 지원 부탁해 장소는 서룡 부성면이야.
This has something to do with the issue I mentioned last time.
이는 지난번에 말씀드린 문제와 관련이 있습니다.
Your order, sir.
주문하셨습니다.
Good
좋은
When did you see them?
언제 보셨나요?
Nearly a month ago.
거의 한 달 전이에요.
"Lieutenant Jae Min Kim"
"김재민 중위"
Okay
좋아요
"Mr. Myung Gil Kim"
"김명길 선생님"
The police are on their way to you.
경찰이 당신을 향해 가고 있습니다.
Concept
개념
The police are coming! Start cleaning!
경찰이 온다! 청소를 시작하세요!
Good. Check if there is a back entrance.
좋은. 뒷문이 있는지 확인해보세요.
Move! quickly
이동하다! 빠르게
Turn off the engine.
엔진을 끄십시오.
Good
좋은
We'll check the general situation, Da Min. Wait here.
전체적인 상황은 저희가 확인해보겠습니다 다민님 여기서 기다리세요.
We arrived before you and searched the place. Nothing happened. It's a flounder farm.
우리가 당신보다 먼저 도착해서 그곳을 수색했지만 아무 일도 일어나지 않았습니다. 가자미 양식장이에요.
Good
좋은
Please talk to the bastard in the trunk.
트렁크에 있는 놈에게 말을 걸어보세요 .
Who is this scoundrel?
이 악당은 누구입니까?
He is Myung-gil's follower.
명길의 추종자이다.
The person who stabbed me.
나를 찔렀던 사람.
I'm a policeman, so answer honestly.
저는 경찰이니 솔직하게 대답해주세요.
Nod your head, you bastard.
고개를 끄덕여라, 이 새끼야.
Is this Sol's fish farm?
여기가 솔이네 양어장인가요?
Does anyone know we're coming?
우리가 오는 걸 아는 사람 있나요?
"Gang Young."
"강영."
This man's comrades ran away in the middle of the fight.
이 남자의 동료들은 싸움 중에 도망갔다.
Maybe they warned them.
어쩌면 그들은 그들에게 경고했을 수도 있습니다.
Leave this man here and get out of here.
이 사람은 여기에 두고 여기서 나가세요.
You weren't here, okay?
당신은 여기 없었어요, 알았죠?
Well
글쎄요 _
- Were you injured? - No.
- 부상을 당하셨나요? - 아니요.
“Han Gu.”
“한구.”
Where is my grandfather?
내 할아버지는 어디 계시나요?
Let's wait. Investigators will get back to us with information about him.
기다리 자. 조사관은 그에 대한 정보를 가지고 우리에게 연락할 것입니다.
There's no time for this.
이럴 시간이 없습니다.
We must find him.
우리는 그를 찾아야 해요.
We will do this no matter what.
우리는 무슨 일이 있어도 이것을 할 것입니다.
The safe, you scoundrel!
금고야, 이 악당아!
Where is Myung Gil Kim's safe?
김명길의 금고는 어디에 있나요?
Damn, unbelievable!
젠장, 말도 안 돼!
You'll die, you bastard, if you stay like this!
이대로 있으면 죽는다 이 새끼야!
Give me a cigarette.
담배 한 대 주세요.
You bastard!
이 개자식!
- Hit me. - You're doomed.
- 날 때려요 - 넌 끝장이야
Hit me harder!
더 세게 때려요!
"Best Pork, Beomseong Distribution Outlet."
"최고의 돼지고기, 범성유통점."
How did it go?
어떻게 됐나요?
What about Mr. Oh?
오 씨는요?
We couldn't find it.
우리는 그것을 찾을 수 없습니다.
I think those bastards took him somewhere else.
내 생각엔 그 놈들이 그를 다른 곳으로 데려간 것 같아.
the curse
저주
Did he say something?
그가 뭔가 말했나요?
He's a stubborn bastard. He won't speak.
그 사람은 완고한 놈이에요. 그는 말을 하지 않을 것이다.
You're having a good time, aren't you?
당신은 좋은 시간을 보내고 있지, 그렇지?
- Do you want to see something more interesting? - What are you saying, you scoundrel?
- 좀 더 재미있는 걸 보고 싶나요? - 무슨 소리야, 이 악당놈?
the curse
저주
my lord! That bastard bit his tongue!
군주! 그 새끼가 혀를 깨물었어!
Damn
젠장
Hurry, sir!
서둘러요!
the curse! Screw it!
저주! 나사로 고정!
- Hey! - Shit.
- 이봐! - 젠장.
- In Beom Kang, wake up. - Damn it!
- 강범인 일어나라 - 젠장!
- Call an ambulance, Woo Jin! - Okay.
- 구급차를 불러라 우진아! - 알았어.
Hey!
여기요!
If we send him, how will we find Myung-gil Kim's safe?
그를 보내면 김명길의 금고를 어떻게 찾을 수 있을까?
However, we cannot afford to let someone die, sir.
하지만 우리는 누군가를 죽게 놔둘 수는 없습니다 .
If he dies, we won't get to the vault.
그가 죽으면 우리는 금고에 갈 수 없습니다.
Damn! Give it to me
젠장! 그걸 나에게주세요
Help me download it please.
다운로드할 수 있도록 도와주세요.
Are you okay sir?
괜찮으세요 선생님?
Wake up sir! Are you well
일어나세요 선생님! 당신은 잘 있습니다
Welcome
환영
Where is the owner?
주인은 어디에 있나요?
On vacation
휴가중
Good
좋은
I want Ethiopian iced coffee.
나는 에티오피아 아이스 커피를 원해요.
Help yourself. Please wait. - Okay, thank you.
알아서 드세요. 기다려주세요 - 네, 감사합니다.
“My happy family, I will keep you safe.”
“행복한 가족 여러분, 제가 지켜드리겠습니다.”
"President Myung-Gil Kim, attached file, video clip."
"김명길 회장님, 첨부파일, 영상클립."
the curse
저주
Hello, Minbeom.
안녕하세요, 민범님.
Myung-Gil Kim still has the video he took of me.
김명길 씨가 찍어준 영상을 아직도 갖고 있어요.
Just sent it to me.
방금 나에게 보냈습니다.
What
무엇
Welcome
환영
"Gang Young"?
'강영'?
the curse
저주
Damn
젠장
Scoundrels.
악당.
You bastard
이 새끼야
salt
소금
What
무엇
Someone was shocked!
누군가 충격을 받았습니다!
- She must be dead. - Check.
- 죽은 게 틀림없어요 - 확인해 보세요
What happened
무슨 일이에요
- Call 911. - I think someone died.
- 911에 전화하세요. - 누군가 죽은 것 같아요.
"Mr. Oh"
"오 씨"
Gun-woo, come on. faster
건우야, 어서. 더 빠르게
You despicable fools.
비열한 바보들아.
Why did you cause a major crisis?
왜 큰 위기를 초래했나요?
What do you want
당신은 무엇을 원하나요
Come to the fish farm today by 9pm.
오늘 밤 9시까지 양어장으로 오세요 .
If you call the police again, I'll chop up In Mok Oh and feed him to the fish.
다시 경찰에 신고하시면 오인목을 썰어서 물고기에게 먹이겠습니다.
Answer me.
대답 해.
I got rid of Gang Young Min and his men, so don't mess with me.
강영민과 그 부하들을 내가 처리했으니 건들지 마세요.
I said I would kill your mother
내가 네 엄마를 죽이겠다고 말했어
If it appears again.
다시 나타나면.
see you there
거기서 보자
"Gang Young"
"강영"
They got Gang Young? But he's a policeman.
강영이 있어요? 하지만 그 사람은 경찰이에요.
The situation will be very dangerous this time.
이번에는 상황이 매우 위험할 것입니다.
We must go alone.
우리는 혼자 가야 해요.
Excuse me
실례합니다
How long have you been there?
거기에 얼마나 있었어?
Since the beginning
처음부터
Don't step aside.
물러서지 마십시오.
I'm going to save my grandfather.
나는 할아버지를 구하러 갈 거예요.
come with me
날 따라와
If something bad happens to Mr. Oh before our eyes,
우리 눈앞에서 오씨에게 안 좋은 일이 생기면
Da Min will inevitably collapse, as happened with Hyun Joo.
다민은 현주처럼 무너질 수밖에 없다 .
I don't want to witness that again, Woo Jin.
다시는 그런 일을 목격하고 싶지 않아, 우진.
But, Gun Woo,
그런데 건우씨,
There is something different from our situation then.
그때의 우리 상황과는 뭔가 다른 것이 있습니다.
Do you know what it is?
그것이 무엇인지 아시나요?
at that time
그때에
The invincible marine duo was scattered.
무적의 해병 듀오가 흩어졌다.
We are not currently divided and we are much stronger. Have you forgotten?
우리는 현재 분열되지 않았고 훨씬 더 강해졌습니다. 너는 잊었 니?
one two three four five
하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯
Okay
좋아요
Therefore,
그러므로,
Let's work together and save everyone.
함께 협력하여 모두를 구합시다.
Mr Oh and Da Min,
오씨와 다민씨,
And everyone Kim hurt.
그리고 김씨 모두가 다쳤어요.
With determination?
결단력 있게?
With determination!
결단력 있게!
Why did you stop us?
왜 우리를 막았나요?
Woo Jin and I will go first. Stay to watch the place.
저랑 우진이 먼저 가겠습니다. 자리에 남아서 지켜보세요.
Move forward once you find a shooting position.
촬영 위치를 찾으면 앞으로 이동하세요.
Seems like a good idea.
좋은 생각인 것 같습니다.
Anzali
안잘리
the curse. He brought me down too far.
저주. 그는 나를 너무 멀리 끌어내렸습니다.
good idea
좋은 생각
What
무엇
You put her down so she wouldn't get hurt, right?
그 사람이 다치지 않도록 내려놓은 거 맞죠?
In fact, I lowered it so we wouldn't get caught.
사실 우리가 들키지 않도록 낮췄어요.
Was it far away?
멀리 있었나요?
It will take ten minutes.
10분 정도 소요됩니다.
Let's finish this quickly on our own.
우리끼리 빨리 끝내자.
good idea
좋은 생각
Kill them!
그들을 죽여 버려!
These bastards have a huge number of weapons.
이 놈들은 엄청난 수의 무기를 가지고 있습니다.
"Woo Jin!"
"우진!"
You bastard!
이 개자식!
Damn
젠장
Leave me, damn it!
날 놔둬, 젠장!
Let me!
허락해주세요!
Damn
젠장
You bastard!
이 개자식!
Oh damn!
아 젠장!
What is this
이게 뭔가요
You bastard!
이 개자식!
Damn
젠장
Hey you
안녕 당신
Can't even get rid of two guys?
두 사람을 없애지도 못하나요?
I'm sorry sir.
죄송해요 선생님.
She always apologizes.
그녀는 항상 사과한다.
And now.
그리고 지금.
Enough
충분한
Hey!
여기요!
If you two bastards take a step,
두 놈이 한발짝 내딛으면
I will cut his throat, so do whatever you want.
목을 벨 테니까 마음대로 하세요.
Okay. They stopped moving.
좋아요. 그들은 움직이지 않았습니다.
What are you doing, you bastards? Hurry and kill them.
뭐하는 거야, 이 개자식들아? 서둘러 그들을 죽여라.
Should I kill them myself?
내가 직접 죽여야 하나?
How amazing you are, you bastards.
정말 대단하다, 이 새끼들아.
Bow down!
엎드려!
- What is this? - What happened?
- 이게 뭐야? - 무슨 일이 일어난 거야?
You vile! Come here
당신은 사악한! 이리 오세요
I said kill them! You bastards!
내가 죽여버리라고 했어! 이 개자식들!
what are you doing? Leave me, you idiot!
뭐하세요? 날 놔둬, 이 바보야!
- Let me! - Let's go to the hospital.
- 할게요! - 병원에 가자.
Kill them! Let's go
그들을 죽여 버려! 갑시다
serious! Are you well
심각한! 당신은 잘 있습니다
This is me, Da Min.
나야, 다민.
She took my eyebrows off.
그녀는 내 눈썹을 떼어냈습니다.
Are you okay, Mr. Oh?
괜찮으세요, 오 선생님?
Thanks
감사해요
What is this
이게 뭔가요
They moved more quickly.
그들은 더 빨리 움직였습니다.
Hurry up and get to work!
서둘러서 일하러 가세요!
Who is Tariq?
타리크는 누구인가?
Chinese food delivery boy.
중국음식 배달아저씨.
What is this, bastards?
이게 뭐야, 개자식들?
Stand your ground, motherfucker!
입장을 고수해라, 개자식아!
They searched the whole area.
그들은 지역 전체를 수색했습니다.
- Search every inch! - What is this place?
- 구석구석 찾아보세요! - 이곳은 무엇인가요?
I find it! Come here everyone!
찾았다! 다들 여기로 오세요!
- Those bastards... - What were they doing here?
- 저 새끼들... - 여기서 뭐하고 있었던 거지?
I'm Yoon Seo-yang, from the Major Crimes Investigation Department.
강력범죄수사과 윤서양 입니다 .
Here's a search warrant.
여기 수색 영장이 있습니다.
We will conduct a search and seize your property.
우리는 수색을 실시하고 귀하의 재산을 압수할 것입니다.
I appreciate your cooperation. Come in.
협조해 주셔서 감사합니다. 올.
Get in quickly.
빨리 들어가세요.
Mr. Jae Min Kim?
김재민 선생님?
You are under arrest for murder, bribery and other charges.
귀하는 살인, 뇌물 수수 및 기타 혐의 로 체포되었습니다 .
the curse. What a worse day.
저주. 정말 더 나쁜 날입니다.
Let's go
갑시다
- Sir. - Yes.
- 선생님 - 네
The warrant was issued quickly so we went to Kim's house.
빨리 영장이 발부되어서 우리는 김씨 집으로 갔다.
Several phones were found in his dresser drawer.
그의 옷장 서랍에서 여러 대의 전화기가 발견되었습니다.
We tracked the numbers, they were all dead or missing people.
숫자를 추적해보니 모두 사망했거나 실종된 사람들이었습니다.
Willah
윌라
This crazy bastard kept the phones of the people he killed.
이 미친 놈은 자신이 죽인 사람들의 휴대폰을 보관하고 있었습니다.
He can't escape this.
그는 이것을 피할 수 없습니다.
Not even the president of America can save him.
미국 대통령도 그를 구할 수는 없습니다.
What about escaping abroad?
해외로 탈출하는 것은 어떻습니까?
He's wanted now, so this won't be easy.
그는 지금 수배 중이므로 쉽지 않을 것입니다.
People often escape to China on cargo ships.
사람들은 종종 화물선을 타고 중국으로 탈출한다.
Kim is a wanted criminal and one of the most dangerous people.
김씨는 수배범이자 가장 위험한 인물 중 한 명이다.
We will intensify surveillance on possible infiltration routes.
침투 경로에 대한 감시를 강화하겠습니다.
He won't flee Korea.
그는 한국을 떠나지 않을 것이다.
But this is not impossible.
그러나 이것이 불가능한 것은 아닙니다.
I see you all think this matter is over, but I'm so nervous right now.
다들 이 일이 끝났다고 생각하시겠지만, 지금은 너무 긴장됩니다.
That bastard still has a video of me.
그 새끼 아직도 내 영상 갖고 있어.
If he loses his mind and spreads it, I will be finished.
그 사람이 정신을 잃고 퍼뜨리면 난 끝이거든요.
"Gang Young."
"강영."
I should see that bastard behind bars.
철창 뒤에 있는 그 놈을 봐야 해요.
"Who day?"
"언제요?"
I understand your position.
나는 당신의 입장을 이해합니다.
But consider Han Guo's condition now.
하지만 지금 한궈의 상태를 생각해 보세요.
And Tae Young hasn't regained consciousness yet.
그리고 태영은 아직 의식을 회복하지 못했습니다.
We need some time.
시간이 좀 필요해요.
I will help you.
내가 당신을 도울 것입니다.
It doesn't end until it's completely over.
완전히 끝날 때까지는 끝나지 않습니다.
Can you find us where Jang Do Im is?
장도임이 있는 곳을 찾아주실 수 있나요?
Why "Jang Do Im"?
왜 '장도임'인가?
Jang Do Im is probably hiding somewhere to stay away from Myung Gil Kim.
장도임은 아마도 김명길을 피해 어딘가에 숨어있을 것이다.
But I think Jang Do Im might know where Myung Gil Kim might flee to.
하지만 장도임은 김명길이 어디로 도망갈지 알고 있을지도 모른다고 생각한다.
True, Jang Do Im may have advised him on how to escape the country.
사실 장도임이 그에게 탈북 방법을 조언했을 수도 있다.
He mentioned that he was responsible for things like this.
그는 이와 같은 일에 책임이 있다고 언급했습니다.
Okay, I'll look into this.
알겠습니다. 조사해 보겠습니다.
How much cash is it?
현금은 얼마인가요?
I can lower the price to 18 million.
가격을 1800만까지 낮출 수 있어요.
Jang Do Im hasn't used a phone or card in his name in the last six months.
장도임은 지난 6개월 동안 본인 명의의 휴대폰이나 카드를 사용한 적이 없습니다.
He avoided everything that could be traced.
그는 추적할 수 있는 모든 것을 피했습니다.
Is there another way?
다른 방법이 있나요?
Well, all we've been able to find so far is his bank account number.
글쎄요, 지금까지 우리가 찾을 수 있었던 것은 그의 은행 계좌번호뿐입니다.
The last cash withdrawal transaction took place in March in Suwon.
마지막 현금인출 거래는 지난 3월 수원에서 이뤄졌다 .
Isn't that enough to find it?
이 정도면 찾을 수 있지 않나?
There are clips that may take a few months of time, so we need someone dedicated to checking them.
몇 달이 걸릴 수 있는 클립이 있기 때문에 이를 확인하는 전담 인력이 필요합니다.
It will take some time.
시간이 좀 걸릴 거예요.
May we have his account number?
그 사람 계좌번호 좀 알 수 있을까요?
This bastard is probably in financial difficulty right now.
이 새끼는 아마 지금 경제적으로 어려움을 겪고 있을 거야.
Transfer the money to that account.
해당 계좌로 돈을 이체하세요.
When sending it, write your phone number in the sender’s name field.
보낼 때 보내는 사람 이름란에 전화번호를 꼭 적어주세요.
Then he will contact you both. This is guaranteed.
그러면 그는 두 사람 모두에게 연락할 것입니다. 이것은 보장됩니다.
- How much should I send? - If it is a large amount, it will do.
- 얼마만큼 보내야 하나요? - 많은 금액이면 보내드립니다.
Ten thousand won?
만원?
I wondered if I should have mentioned that last time,
지난번 에 언급했어야 했는지 궁금하네요 .
But in our field, this is what we mean by “a large amount,” which varies.
그러나 우리 분야에서는 이것이 '많은 양'을 의미하는 것으로 다양합니다.
The large sum she intended for Kang's personal data,
그녀가 강씨의 개인정보를 위해 의도한 거액은 ,
It was supposed to be a million , not 10,000.
10000이 아니라 10000000000000000000000000000000000이 아니라 000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000이 아니라 000000000000000000000으로 되어 있었습니다 .
1 million won?
100만원?
Of course, it's not my intention to demand this money from you now.
물론, 지금 당신에게 이 돈을 요구할 생각은 없습니다 .
I'm not stingy.
나는 인색하지 않습니다.
We are a family.
우리는 가족입니다.
How much are we talking about in our situation?
우리 상황에서 우리는 얼마나 많은 이야기를 하고 있습니까?
He won't be satisfied with a million won.
그는 백만원에 만족하지 않을 것이다.
Ten million won.
천만 원.
And he will come immediately.
그러면 그는 즉시 올 것이다.
Your wounds do not heal because you continue to drink alcohol...
술을 계속 마셔서 상처가 아물지 않는데..
the curse
저주
- Doctor. - Yes, sir.
- 박사님 - 네, 선생님
Just do your job.
그냥 일을 하세요.
Your order, sir.
주문하셨습니다.
Damn
젠장
‫66،‬
66,
‫67،‬
67,
‫68، 69.‬
68, 69.
"Woo Jin."
"우진."
No number appears.
번호가 나타나지 않습니다.
Welcome
환영
You are the young man
당신은 청년입니다
The one who was with President Choi, right?
최 회장과 함께 있던 사람 맞죠?
its me
나야
The police told you my account number.
경찰이 내 계좌번호를 알려줬어요.
What is the matter? Did you send me money?
문제가 무엇입니까? 나에게 돈을 보냈나요?
Myung Gil Kim escaped.
김명길은 탈출했다.
Why
왜
The police raided Myung Gil Kim's house and found evidence that he killed people.
경찰은 김명길의 집을 급습 해 그가 사람을 죽였다는 증거를 찾아냈다.
When did that happen
언제 그런 일이 일어났나요?
Two days ago
이틀 전
You know where he's going to run, right?
그 사람이 어디로 달려갈지 아시죠?
Yes I know
네, 알아요
Please
제발
We want to catch Myung Gil Kim. help us
김명길을 잡고 싶다. 우리를 도와 줘
how much will you pay
얼마를 지불할 것인가?
A large amount.
많은 양.
Damn, you've got to be kidding me.
젠장, 농담하는 거겠죠?
- A billion! - A billion?
- 10억! - 10억?
I trusted Chairman Choi and my situation worsened.
최 회장을 믿었고 상황은 더욱 악화됐다.
I deserve this amount of compensation.
나는 이 정도의 보상을 받을 자격이 있다.
But currently, we only have...
하지만 현재 우리에겐...
Within four days, Myung Gil Kim will flee out of the country by the means I told him about.
나흘 안에 김명길 씨는 제가 알려드린 방법으로 국외로 도피할 것입니다.
You know my account, right?
내 계좌 아시죠?
think about it
그것에 대해 생각해보세요
unbelievable
믿을 수 없는
Where will we get a billion?
10억은 어디서 구할 수 있나요?
Should we ask Mr. Oh?
오씨한테 물어볼까?
Mr. Oh has no money.
오씨는 돈이 없다.
The money he gave us was the last available money.
그가 우리에게 준 돈은 마지막 남은 돈이었습니다.
Wait.
기다리다.
How many are here?
여기에는 몇 명이 있나요?
I think about 300 million.
300억 정도 생각하고 있습니다.
Much less than we want.
우리가 원하는 것보다 훨씬 적습니다.
Should we ask for it from Min Beom?
민범한테 물어볼까?
Jang Do Im is the one who filmed that video for Min Beom.
민범의 영상을 촬영한 사람이 장도임 이다.
Do you think it will help us implement this?
이것이 우리가 이것을 구현하는 데 도움이 될 것이라고 생각하십니까?
But Min Beom is the only one who has that kind of money.
그런데 그런 돈을 가진 사람 은 민범뿐이다 .
Let's ask him for once, okay?
그 사람한테 한 번 물어보자, 알았지?
Here they are, sir.
여기 있습니다.
Do you trust Jang Do Im?
장도임을 믿으시나요?
In reality
실제로는
We think we can trust the information he has.
우리는 그가 가지고 있는 정보를 신뢰할 수 있다고 생각합니다.
What should I do if he takes the billion and flees the country?
만약 그 사람이 10억을 가지고 나라를 떠나면 어떻게 해야 합니까 ?
What will we do then?
그러면 우리는 무엇을 할 것인가?
Jang Do Im breaks his promise and runs away
장도임은 약속을 어기고 도망친다.
We will chase him until we catch him.
우리는 그를 잡을 때까지 그를 쫓아갈 것입니다.
I can promise you that.
나는 그것을 약속할 수 있다.
Make sure you keep this promise.
이 약속을 꼭 지키세요.
- I'll do it. - Okay.
- 내가 할게요 - 알았어
“I received a billion won.”
“10억 받았어요.”
Okay, I'm done checking it out. Go ahead.
알겠습니다. 확인을 마쳤습니다. 계속하세요.
Good
좋은
you can go
당신은 갈 수 있습니다
"Pohang Station"
"포항역"
"Anonymous caller"
"익명의 발신자"
Write
쓰다
The day after tomorrow at 1pm, a ship called Nike will depart from Pohang.
모레 오후 1시에 나이키라는 배가 포항에서 출발합니다.
To Ho Chi Minh City.
호치민으로.
Kim gave political funding to a high-ranking Vietnamese official.
김 위원장은 베트남 고위 관리에게 정치 자금을 지원했습니다 .
He will leave with all the money he has hidden.
그는 숨겨둔 돈을 모두 가지고 떠날 것이다.
The container number is “TJBU 9004230”.
컨테이너 번호는 "TJBU 9004230"입니다.
His money will be hidden in a container inside the truck.
그의 돈은 트럭 내부의 컨테이너에 숨겨져 있을 것입니다.
Should we move when he gets on the ship?
그가 배에 오르면 우리는 움직여야 할까요?
It's a big ship and won't be easy to find.
배는 커서 찾기가 쉽지 않을 것 같아요.
How do we find it?
어떻게 찾을 수 있나요?
Board the ship with him!
그와 함께 배에 탑승하세요!
You mean we take it to Vietnam?
베트남으로 가져간다는 뜻인가요?
This is your decision.
이것은 귀하의 결정입니다.
- I'll end the call now. - Wait.
- 이제 통화를 끊겠습니다 - 잠깐만요
What should we do if we want to get on that ship?
그 배에 오르고 싶다면 어떻게 해야 할까요 ?
I will send you the data of one of my acquaintances. Tell him that I sent you and come to an agreement with him.
제가 아는 지인의 데이터를 보내드리니 제가 보냈다고 말씀드리고 합의를 하세요.
And for your information, he likes to get paid in cash.
그리고 참고로 그 사람은 돈을 현금으로 받는 걸 좋아한다고 하더군요.
We received the message.
우리는 메시지를 받았습니다.
I didn't know what you needed, so I prepared a bunch of everything for you.
나는 당신에게 무엇이 필요한지 몰랐기 때문에 당신을 위해 모든 것을 준비했습니다.
Thank you sir.
감사합니다.
Take care of yourself.
몸 조심하세요.
Okay sir.
알겠습니다.
We agreed
우리는 동의했다
Let's go upstairs.
위층으로 가자.
You beat me.
네가 날 이겼어.
I want to talk to them.
나는 그들과 이야기하고 싶다.
Good
좋은
Thank you both for your help.
도움을 주셔서 감사합니다.
We are the ones who should thank you.
감사해야 할 사람은 바로 우리입니다.
Goodbye, Da Min.
안녕, 다민.
Good-bye
안녕히 가세요
Help yourself
알아서 드세요
You know my number, right?
내 전화번호는 알지?
Let's go
갑시다
- Yes, Min Beom. - Are you on the way?
- 네, 민범님 - 지금 가시나요?
We're on the way.
가는 중이에요.
Don't get hurt.
상처받지 마세요.
Good
좋은
Gang Young and I will handle the rest.
나머지는 강영이랑 내가 할게.
drive carefully
조심해서 운전해
Good
좋은
Let's hurry.
서두르 자.
Wait a minute.
잠깐 기다려요.
Moment
순간
"Woo Jin."
"우진."
Good
좋은
Let's sail.
항해하자.
- Let's check out the inside of the ship first. - With determination!
- 먼저 배 내부부터 살펴볼까요 - 결단력 있게!
With determination!
결단력 있게!
Myung Gil Kim!
김명길!
the curse
저주
Okay
좋아요
If she shows up again...
만약 그녀가 다시 나타난다면...
I will kill you.
나는 당신을 죽일 것입니다.
“Gun-woo.”
“건우.”
Are you well
당신은 잘 있습니다
What is the matter
무슨 문제야?
"Woo Jin."
"우진."
I think I've become a troll.
아무래도 트롤이 된 것 같아요.
Gun Woo, did you forget the boxer's heart?
건우 씨, 복서의 마음을 잊으셨나요?
We just have to find a way back to it.
우리는 그것으로 돌아갈 길을 찾아야만 합니다.
We agreed? Let's get back together.
우리는 동의했다? 다시 만나자.
Good
좋은
Let's go back.
돌아가자.
Give me your hand.
나에게 손을 내밀어.
Wow! "Woo Jin!"
우와! "우진!"
Wow, we found it!
와, 찾았어요!
Welcome
환영
- Where are you, Min Beom? - I'm almost there.
- 민범 씨는 어디 있어요? - 거의 다 왔어요.
Did you find the gold bars?
금괴를 찾았나요?
Yes, we found them all.
예, 모두 찾았습니다.
And the phone?
그리고 전화는요?
I'll go get him.
내가 그를 데리러 갈게요.
- Woo Jin, here. - Okay.
- 우진아 여기야 - 알았어
- Yes. - Let's go.
- 그래 가자.
How did things go?
일이 어떻게 됐나요?
I finally got the phone.
드디어 전화를 받았어요.
Well done.
잘하셨어요.
I requested support from Interpol. They will wait in Vietnam.
인터폴에 지원을 요청했는데 베트남에서 기다릴 거예요.
The crisis is over.
위기는 끝났습니다.
I suffered greatly, my young friend.
나는 큰 고통을 겪었다, 나의 젊은 친구여.
Thank you, Gang Young.
고마워요 강영님.
What would you like to do?
무엇을하고 싶으십니까?
Mr. Choi has always wanted to help the poor receive decent health care,
최씨는 항상 가난한 사람들이 적절한 의료 서비스를 받을 수 있도록 돕고 싶었습니다.
Therefore, I would like this money to be used for what Mr. Choi wished.
그러므로 나는 이 돈을 최씨가 바라는 대로 사용하기를 원합니다 .
What do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
Don't you want money for yourself?
너 자신을 위해 돈을 원하지 않니?
I definitely want to.
나는 확실히하고 싶다.
But that's not my money.
하지만 그건 내 돈이 아닙니다.
I returned Mr. Choi's good deed for his kindness.
나는 최씨의 친절에 보답했다.
I kept my promise to him.
나는 그와의 약속을 지켰다.
Good
좋은
My friend.
내 친구.
We have 168 bars, each weighing seven kilograms.
우리는 각각의 무게가 7kg인 168개의 막대를 가지고 있습니다 .
Each of them is worth 500 million at its current price, meaning in total, approximately 84 billion.
각각의 가치는 현재 가격으로 5억 달러, 총 가치는 약 840억 달러입니다.
If you want, we can take it
원하시면 저희가 가져가겠습니다
To establish a social welfare institution under the name “AIL” Group.
AIL그룹이라는 이름으로 사회복지기관을 설립한다 .
Through this institution, we will be able to provide medical assistance to those in need.
이 기관을 통해 우리는 도움이 필요한 사람들에게 의료 지원을 제공할 수 있을 것입니다.
Or should I ask our company to add an amount of money
아니면 우리 회사에 금액을 추가해달라고 요청해야 할까요?
To establish a hospital?
병원을 차리려면?
-That sounds like a great idea. -Doesn't it?
- 좋은 생각인 것 같군요. - 그렇죠?
It's a great
정말 대단해요
I think my father will like it.
아버지가 좋아하실 것 같아요.
I believe this will help us improve our company image.
나는 이것이 우리 회사 이미지를 향상시키는 데 도움이 될 것이라고 믿습니다.
We also contribute to doing good.
우리는 또한 선한 일을 하는 데 기여합니다.
I will start creating it as soon as I finish the hotel issue.
호텔 이슈가 끝나는 대로 제작에 착수하겠습니다 .
Min Beom, would you please include Mr. Choi in the hospital name?
민범 씨, 병원 이름에 최 씨를 넣어주실 수 있나요?
-What was his name? -Tae Ho Choi.
- 그 사람 이름이 뭐였더라? - 최태호.
Honestly, this won't be easy.
솔직히 이게 쉽지는 않을 것 같아요.
But I will keep this in mind.
하지만 나는 이것을 명심하겠습니다.
I thank you
감사합니다
What
무엇
I will pay the shortfall with my own money.
부족분은 내 돈으로 갚겠습니다.
Consider it a reward for your mastery of what you did.
당신이 한 일에 대한 숙달에 대한 보상이라고 생각하십시오.
No need for that. I am completely satisfied.
그럴 필요는 없습니다. 나는 완전히 만족합니다.
Mr. Choi would have done the same.
최씨도 그랬을 것이다.
Take them.
가져가세요.
Don't you know what you're saying?
무슨 말인지 모르시나요?
"Thank you" is enough for me.
"고마워요" 한 마디면 충분해요.
Thank you, Mr. Choi.
고마워요, 최 선생님.
On the contrary.
반대로.
I'm the one who should thank you.
감사해야 할 사람은 바로 나다.
Thank you very much
매우 감사합니다
Pick it up!
그것을 집어!
- No! - Let's go!
- 안돼 - 가자!
- I'll come. - Here.
- 갈게요 - 여기요
I will come.
나는 올 것이다.
This too
이것도
Hello, Gun Woo.
안녕하세요, 건우님.
Where are you
어디세요
Hey! “Gun-woo!”
여기요! “건우!”
My dear son.
내 사랑하는 아들.
"Woo Jin."
"우진."
What happened to your face?
얼굴에 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
You both suffered.
두 분 모두 고생하셨습니다.
The crisis is over, mom. Let's go home.
위기는 끝났어요, 엄마. 집에 가자.
Good
좋은
I'm so proud of you both.
나는 너희 둘 다 정말 자랑스럽다.
Translation of "Walid Muharram"
"왈리드 무하람"의 번역